So if you're looking out for a structured DS algorithm course, I must say you're on the correct channel.
So in this video I'll be telling you how the learn DS algorithm from A to Z in depth. Yes.
So first of all, where to learn not on the YouTube channel because it is not structured.
You'll have to head over to the website, take you forward.org might be seeing it on the screen.
The UI might be different. Someone's down the line, but doesn't matter.
Which course is it? Something as A to Z DSA course. Open it up.
And as 4 55 modules, covering 18 or 19 topics. Every topic has sub modules like sub parts as well.
So there are a bunch of problems that you will be solving in this particular course.
Is it paid? No, it is absolutely free. And it covers a lot more problems than what the
course is. Well, you can buy any of the paid courses and you can have a comparison done as well.
So the next question, how do you get the best output of this particular course?
First of all, the course has like every topic has some theory and every topic has some problems.
Rather a lot of problems. For the theory part, what I will say is watch out the videos.
Just watch out the videos and do not dive the just more the topic and then start solving problems.
Because in DSA I'll go, a theory is not that important. Solving problems is important because
that will help you to develop the problem solving ability. Got it. So watch out the videos.
Do not dive much and then start solving problems. Stempice. Pick up a problem according to the
problem. Now when I'm saying, try out that problem means if you have a extreme naive solution,
extreme brute solution hit it convert your thought process into the code right it and some method
doesn't work doesn't matter. It de blocks there are blocks attached to every problem and solutions are
categorized if a problem has multiple solution you'll find categorized. So you can read out all of them.
If you're not able to understand, watch out the videos and for every problem that you're not
able to understand or there is something new. Create nodes so that you can revise afterwards.
Right? And then again, re-try whatever solution you have learned. Retry without watching the video
without watching the block. Retry. This should be your method of learning. Got it. And this is how you
can get the best output. But in order to get a accelerated output, what I will recommend you is
to get a mentor from pre-placed. A pre-placed is a website which offers amazing mentors.
The mentors who are working at fan companies or in-depth talk product based companies. So if you get
a mentor, what will happen is they will have a personalized roadmap. Along with DSS system design,
low level design, whatever you require, they'll give you a personalized roadmap and they'll have
it online check. One week for arrays. After one week, hey did you complete arrays? Let's have a
lot of resources on system design. Low level design, DSL go and other things project ideas. Since
this people work in industry, they know how everything works. So they'll be giving you project ideas as
well. After that, once you're prepared, you will be able to have mock interviews with them before
the real interview. Resume reviews. According to the jobs that you are applying, you can ask them to
review your resumes. You can have refills from them as well and from their friends as well. And right
the end, you can have a personalized discount code from them. So if you are liking a mentor,
ask them for a discount coupon code. They will be giving you if they do not, you can use
Striva 1000 for an extra 1000 threads. So anyway, we got the link in the description. You can
book a free trial session with any of the mentor. It's absolutely free. Go and check it out.
So let's head over to the next part. Covered to right scam. So there is a lot of misinformation in the market
because it's not paid. It's actually taking a lot of businesses. As I said, we have 90
lakh visits on this course in the last 1.5 years. So first of all, the first thing that everyone
is saying is this course is in C++. Absolute garbage absolute nonsense. So I have one video
the initial video that that says C++ in one shot. That's it. That's it. Haven't made the video
in one shot. But apart from this video, you pick up any topic. I'm throwing an open challenge.
Pick up any topic. Arase, trees, DP, grass, any of the topics. We'll find that I write
pseudo code. I don't write code in C++. And in my blogs, we are attaching blogs,
notes to every problem. We'll find C++ Java Python JavaScript codes. So we are not teaching C++.
The entire course is in pseudo code. You're focusing on problem solving. Right?
As a second thing is it's not beginner friendly. This is something which everyone
like the influence is spreading to because it's a free course. So what I'll ask you to do is
and not say anything. Each of the many of you seniors who are who got recently placed.
As them, here's this guy's driver. Should we follow him? Should we follow the
rivals? He to set the AC course. You can find reviews on building. You can find reviews on Twitter,
and in any way you wish to. Post it to people will tell you the reviews of this course. Do not
ask an influencer or anyone who is running a business around this one. Got it? It is absolutely
big enough. And that is why it has 450 5 modules. But I start from easy, then go to medium. And
then I cover a lot of advanced problems with a lot of paid courses in the market of a lot of
basic, easy, in depth. And when it comes to medium and hard, they tend to skip. You can pick up any
of the free DSC courses. They will end up at 170, 180, 200 at max. And they'll be skipping the
advanced problems or they'll be doing three or four of them. But over here, now, of course,
we do a bunch of advanced problems. So it has stuff, but in order to exceed, you need to do
any, frankly, the course has around 250 to 300 concepts or problems for every concept at multiple
problems. So if you are understanding a concept, it might have a four, four, four problems.
So you can solve two and you can skip the rest two. That is your wish. It's not necessarily
to solve 455. I've given them per practice for your betterment. Got it. The next thing.
Along with the course, what else should you do? One thing is an absolute must,
quantities. Head over to read code. So basically, need code. There's a website as read code,
head over to court forces. Give every point this. So there is something in the market that,
like a lot of bigness thing that I should learn everything. And then I should start appearing for
contest. Do not do that. You know, basic programming, start appearing on the contest.
Even if you're able to solve one problem, that is absolutely fine. Give every contest for the next
two years. Give every contest along with learning DS algorithm. To be able to learn,
you'll come back and say me, you wear correct, giving contest actually helped me to learn, because
it's a lot of new concepts, a lot of new unseen problems. So you'll learn a lot, lot more, got it.
So to be leaving out the link of this particular A2 set, DSC course, in the description, I'll
leaving out the link of pre-placed. You can book free trial with any of the mentors you wish to
and get onboarded with them. If you haven't fallen beyond, social media, I'll be leaving out all the
social media handles in the description as well. With this, I'll be wrapping up this video. Make sure
to follow the website, not the YouTube channel. With this, I'll be wrapping up this video. Let's