the trippy by NB files and you are free to collaborate with your classmates but just try the
name of the people you collaborated with at the top of the worksheet. So, as is introduced
the worksheet still by the worksheet two ways on simple linear regression and down multiple
linear regression. You will have to just plot a scatter plot and build a linear regression model
which have to check if it follows the OS assumptions and validate the linear regression model.
Then the multiple linear regression have to plot a corralogram and check which contribute
most to the target variable and build a multiple linear regression model based on that.
Worksheep 2B is based on rich regression, last so and elastic regression. You have to
build all these three models. Worksheep 2B is on logistic regression. You have to just build
logistic regression model and you are the ROC curve and a ROC value. So, the last data summit will be
28 September. Before constructing the core core logogram you can use anything label and coding
one more thing. This can ask your doubts in the chat or you can raise your hand will unmute you.
There will be another creation four or five days before that it lines. So, by then your
portion should be covered. So, you will be able to solve and ask more questions at time.
But if you have any doubts you can put it in the chat or unmute or raise your hand will unmute.
You can just use the libraries to build the model. Like for linear regression model you can use
LM and for worksheet 2B you can use GLM net. You need not build one from scan just import the
life duties. You can use any library you want. There is no compression on the syntax you can use
any libraries. Which question the OLS assumptions? For OLS assumptions you can do like three. You can
check if the residuals are residuals for the normal distribution. You can check with homosadacity
and you can check for the linear relationship. You can do three that is enough.
Let us answer your question. If you did as a map down it will be better and professional. If it is
code then use the code. Both graphs and write ups because try to add your analysis as much as possible
not only code. So, add comments or map down whatever you are plotting. Ignase you can unmute and
pause the question.
So, you can add a map down cell and answer in that cell after each question.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I do. The histogram of residuals is in the normal distribution. But do
add like a text. I will just do not add the code. I do not write the code for plotting
whatever you want to write the text or analysis and code cells when you want to execute the code.
Add there any more questions or mission random. There will be another T.S. session
profile days before the deadline. So, you guys should the portion should be covered by then.
So, you guys should be able to solve that. About the hackathon we will let you know. So,
you guys have any more questions. Okay. We lent them. Thank you for joining us.
If any of you have missed the first part of this session, you'll make the recording available.
You guys can catch up with that. Thank you.