the tripp by NB file and you are free to collaborate with your classmates but just try the
name of the people you collaborate with at the top of the worksheet. I just introduced the
worksheets to you guys. Workheets to ways on simple linear regression and down multiple linear
regression will have to just plot a scatter plot and build a linear regression model.
Why you have to check if it follows the OS assumptions and validate the linear regression model.
Then the multiple linear regression have to plot a corollogram and check which contributes
most to the target variable and build a multiple linear regression model based on that.
Workheets will be based on a rich regression, last so and elastic regression you have to build
all these three models. Workheets both these are logistic regression, you have to just build a logistic
regression model and the ROC curve and new machine value. So the last data summit will be
28 September. Before constructing the corollogram you can use anything label encoding or
one more 10 code. This can ask your doubts in the chat or you can raise your hand will unmute.
You will be another 28 session or four five days before that it lines. So by then your portion
should be covered so you will be able to solve and ask more questions that time. If you have any doubts
you can written the chat or unmute or raise your hand will unmute.
Can just use the libraries to build the model. Like for linear regression model you can use LM
for worksheet to be you can use GLM net. You need not build one from scan just import the
library. You can use any library you want. There is no compression on the syntax you can use any
syntax or any libraries. Which question the OS assumptions? For all the assumptions you can
do like three. You can check if the residuals are residuals for the normal distribution.
Can check for homosadacity and you can check for the linear relationship. You can do three.
That's an other answer your question. If you did as a mark down it will be better and professional.
If you answer in terms of if it's four then use the code. Both graphs and write ups
because try to add your analysis as much as possible not only code so add comments or
mark down whatever you are plotting. Ignate you can unmute and ask the question.
Okay.
So that's what I answer. You can add a mark down sale and answer in that cell after each
question.
Yes.
Yeah I do and the histogram of residuals is in a phenomenal distribution. But do add like
or text else you just don't add the code. Just don't write the code for the plotting
histogram and you will add analysis of the graph. Mark down code just add mark down sales.
Whenever you want to write the text or analysis then code sales when you want to execute the code.
There are any more questions or shall end them. There'll be another session
of the day before the deadline. So the portion should be covered by the
so you guys should be able to solve that. About the hackathon will let you know.
You guys have any more questions. Okay. That will end them. Thank you for joining.
If any of you missed the first part of this session you'll make the recording available.
You guys can catch up with that. Thank you.